(Leonard:)And I can't play
because I'm going with her. Right?
Uh, yeah, if you want.
There may not be room.
(Penny:)He's got a lot of stuff, like guitars
and amplifiers.
(Leonard:)Wait. What are you talking about?
(Penny:)My friend Justin.
(Sheldon:)Pay attention, Leonard.
That's why she can't play on Sunday.
(Leonard:)-Who is this Justin?
-Your turn.
(Penny:)-I told you about him.
-Roll the dice.
(Penny:)Yeah. My friend from Omaha,
plays the guitar.
(Penny:)He's coming
looking for session work.
(Penny:)So I told him
he could crash on my couch.
Come on. Roll a six, Penny dies horribly
in a nuclear meltdown.
(Sheldon:)See what I mean
when I say the fun is real?
(Leonard:)Hang on. Some guy
is gonna be sleeping on your couch?
(Penny:)He's not some guy. He's my friend.
(Leonard:)So by friend, do you mean
"friend" friend...
...gay friend, or "ex-boyfriend
you're now platonic with...
...but still might have a thing for you"
friend?
(Penny:)Well, he's definitely not gay.
Oh. A definitely-not-gay musician
sleeping on my girlfriend's couch.
Yippie.
(Penny:)Okay, we went out a little bit
a long time ago.